有意思
Interesting.
好的
Okay.
多糟糕
How bad is it?
我这么说吧
Let me put it this way--
你有三尺白绫跟板凳吗
do you own a barrel and suspenders?
你是说认真的吗
Are you serious?
我戴这个遮光帽可不是为了打女子高尔夫
I'm not wearing this visor to play women's golf.
绿色遮光帽是19世纪晚期到20世纪中期
会计审计员等都会戴来遮挡早期白炽灯光线
我猜猜
Oh, let me guess.
你们在玩梦幻会计公司
You guys are drafting your fantasy accounting firms.
我们在帮忙拉杰整理财务状况
We're helping Raj figure out his finances.
他有工作收入  情况能有多差
Well, he has a job. How bad can it be?
他的房租与汽车租贷费用极其高
Well, his rent and car lease are exceedingly high.
再加上他喜欢上馆子吃饭与购物
You couple that with his penchant for dining out and shopping...
等等  购物不是指买衣服对吧
Wait, wait, not shopping for clothes, right?
看他这打扮...
Because look.
而且他的信用卡债务数额惊人
He also has a remarkable amount of credit card debt.
不是你爹帮你付的信用卡账单吗
I thought your dad paid your cards.
我有一张自己付款的紧急备用卡
I have a card for emergencies that I pay for myself.
在洛城动物园发生了什么紧急事故
What emergency happened at the L.A. Zoo?
我认养了一只企鹅
That's a penguin I sponsor.
它们因为全球暖化而失去了家园
They're losing their homes to global warming,
而我的车每三公里耗一升油
and my car gets, like, seven miles a gallon,
我挺过意不去
so I felt bad.
这粉嫩双颊[屁股]是啥
What is Pink Cheeks?
是私密处除毛  那张不许看
It's intimate waxing. Quit looking at that!
或许你该找个人
Maybe you should find someone
来帮忙让你财务状况回到正轨
to help you get your finances under control.
比如理财经理吗
Like a business manager?
不  当然不行
No, absolutely not.
你请不起一名
You can't afford to hire someone
会禁止你花钱在白痴开销上的人
who'll forbid you from spending your money on foolish expenses.
因为那也是白痴开销  而我禁止你这么做
That is a foolish expense, and I forbid it.
那如果有一个单纯只是喜欢控制别人
What if there's someone who just likes controlling
而且乐于将别人生活中的欢乐偷走的人呢
other people and stealing joy from their lives?
他听起来像个反社会变态啊
He sounds like a sociopath.
我们也不确定  他妈妈没带他去检查过这个
We don't know, his mother never had him tested.
你们说的是我  真好笑
You're talking about me. Very funny.
虽然我的确是会享受安排好预算
Although I would enjoy drawing up a budget
然后逼拉杰坚持计划
and forcing Raj to adhere to it
而且丝毫不带任何同情心
without an ounce of compassion.
等等  那谁去跟企鹅说金援要断了
Wait, wait, who's gonna break it to the penguin?
行啊  谢尔顿
Okay, Sheldon.
我的财务就交给你管吧
Yeah, I'm putting you in charge of my finances.
我再也不会花任何一分未经你批准的钱
I will not spend another penny that you don't authorize.
非常好
Very well.
漫展的票这周五开卖
Hey, Comic-Con tickets go on sale this Friday.
你不许买
You can't buy one.
祝你下次好运啦  粉嫩双颊
Oh, better luck next time, Pink Cheeks.
你真的要去漫展吗
You're actually going to Comic-Con?
莱纳德希望我多陪他做这方面的事
Well, Leonard wants me to do more stuff like that with him,
我就想要不今年陪他去
so I thought maybe this year I'd tag along.
真好  我猜你一定会玩得很开心
Well, that's sweet. I bet you'll have fun.
那你要一起来吗
So, do you want to come?
谢邀  不用了
No, thanks.
我已经住在一个所有阿宅都会来的家了
I already live in a place all the nerds come to.
求你啦  我上个月也陪你参加无聊活动了啊
Please? I went to your boring thing last month.
你是说我阿姨的葬礼吗
My aunt's funeral?
干嘛啊  你自己也在听悼词时看邮箱了
Come on, even you checked your e-mail during the eulogy.
我才不要去
Well, I'm not going,
但我觉得你想去挺好的
but I do think it's nice you want to.
不是我想去好吗
It's not that I want to go,
我只是想哄莱纳德高兴
I just think it'll make Leonard happy.
如果哄他就得看他挤进伊渥克服
And if I have to watch him squeeze into an Ewok costume,
那我也忍了
so be it.
看看你  要去漫展
Look at you, going to Comic-Con,
还聊起了伊渥克族
talking about Ewoks.
我真变成了我们这群里最酷的那个人了
I really have become the cool one around here.
你真认为佩妮会在漫展玩得开心吗
You actually think Penny will have fun at Comic-Con?
不觉得  所以这会让我很郁闷
No. Which will make me miserable,
而通常让我郁闷是谢尔顿的专利
which is usually Sheldon's job.
她一定会很不爽排队等明星座谈会
She's gonna hate waiting in line for the panels.
她一定会很不爽去听座谈会的阿宅
She's gonna hate all the crowds at the panels.
她一定会很不爽那些座谈会
She's gonna hate the panels.
她一定会很不爽我们说"座谈会"这词的频率
She's gonna hate how often we say the word "Panels."
那你干嘛不叫她别来了
Why don't you just tell her not to come?
她感觉超有兴致  我不想这么狠心
Well, she's so excited, I can't do that to her.
那你何不把漫展说得一文不值
What if you make it sound so bad
她就自己不会想去啦
she won't want to go?
那我倒是可以狠心试试
That I would do to her.
真不敢相信佩妮都去了
I can't believe Penny's gonna get to go,
而我却不能去
and I'm not.
反正你可以在网上看明星座谈会嘛
You can always watch the panels online.
天啊  我们还真是总说"座谈会"
Oh, boy, we do say that a lot.
座谈会
Panels.
我就想加入一下大家
Just wanted to be included.
求你了  谢尔顿  这可是漫展
Come on, Sheldon, it's Comic-Con.
让我花钱去参加吧
Just let me have the money for this,
我保证不会乱花钱干别的
and I won't ask for anything else.
是你让我来管着你的账
You put me in charge of your finances.
如果你想要心软没骨气  让你颐指气使的人
If you wanted someone weak and spineless you could walk all over,
你当初就该去找莱纳德来管
you should have asked Leonard.
你看  郁闷吧
See? Miserable.
行  你说得没错  是我自作自受
Okay, you're right, I got myself into this,
但每年都是我们四个一起去参加漫展的啊
but I've never missed a Comic-Con with you guys.
你老爸愿意宠溺你  但我可以不会
Your father may have spoiled you, but I won't.
如果你想要去动漫展的票
If you want a ticket to Comic-Con,
那我建议你想办法去挣点外快
I suggest you figure out a way to earn the money yourself.
你是个受过高度教育的成人
Yeah, you're a grown man who's highly educated.
你可以收钱当人肉沙包啊
You could charge people money to punch you.
随你嘲讽  我不知道你哪来的自信
Go ahead, make jokes. I don't know why you think
觉得自己就去得成漫展  你家小孩刚出生
you're going to Comic-Con-- you just had a baby.
-所以呢  -还所以呢
- So? - Well, so?
所以你觉得伯纳黛特会轻松答应
So you think Bernadette's just gonna let you
让你飞去圣地亚哥五天
jet down to San Diego for five days
然后把她孤零零丢在家吗
and leave her alone?
稍等一下
Hang-hang on.
所以我得带着佩妮  而你付不起票
So I have to bring Penny, you can't afford it,
霍华德去就死定了
Howard's gonna get in trouble,
唯独这家伙可以好好享受漫展
and this guy gets to have a great time.
我要打扮成邓布利多去
I'm gonna go as Dumbledore.
我亲爱的小美人好吗
How's my favorite girl?
还可以啊
Okay.
-你在干嘛呢  -做千层面
- What you doing? - Making lasagna.
这妞出得了厅堂  又入得了厨房
Oh, she's sexy, she can cook.
我真是走了大运
I'm such a lucky guy.
你想买傻逼东西了  还是你做傻逼事了
You want something stupid, or you did something stupid?
才不是  我只是走进来  看到闭月羞花的你
No. I just walked in here, saw how beautiful you are
情不自禁就想说出口
and had to tell you.
天啊  你是不是背着我跟拉杰搞基了
Oh, dear God, you're cheating on me with Raj.
这笑话真是永不过时
Never gets old.
好啦  我的确想要个东西
Okay, there is something I want,
不过不是什么大事
but it's not a big deal.
什么东西
What is it?
漫展的票这周五开卖
Well, Comic-Con tickets go on sale this Friday,
我希望能跟其他几个一起去
and I was hoping I could go with the guys.
但在你回答之前  我会对我的离开做出补偿
But before you say anything, I'll make up for being gone
家里一切活我全包  做什么都行
by doing everything around here-- I mean everything.
连帮你回答这个问题都行
I'm even gonna answer for you.
"准了  霍华德  准你去"
"Yes, Howard, you can go."
拒绝你真是太难了
It's so hard to say no to you.
谢谢你
Thank you.
所以或许吧
So I'll say maybe.
什么  为什么
What? Why?
你自己说票周五才开卖对吧
You said tickets don't go on sale till Friday, right?
对啊
Yeah.
你也说家里一切活你全包对吧
You said you were gonna do all this stuff for me, right?
对啊
Yeah.
听出我接下来要说什么了吗
See where I'm going with this?
听出来了
Yeah.
如果你不知道怎么做千层面  就去问谷歌
If you don't know how to make lasagna, Google does.
好的  所以这是动漫展主层
Okay, so this is the main Comic-Con floor.
所有的小贩和展览都在这里
It's where all the vendors and exhibits are.
好多人挤在这里面啊
Wow, that is a lot of people jammed in there.
有时候霍华德会穿条纹衫
I know. Sometimes Howard wears a striped shirt
这样我们就能玩"霍华德在哪里"
so we can play "Where's Wolowitz?"
知名游戏童书《威利在哪里》  就是在人海中
找出身穿红白条纹衫与绒球帽的男主人翁
这是我们餐风露宿排队
Okay, now, th-this is us camping out in line
等去看《复仇者联盟》座谈会
for the Avengers panel.
你们还真睡在人行道上呢
Oh, you really sleep on the sidewalk, huh?
对啊  入夜有时挺冷
Yeah. It can get chilly,
但拉杰想出  如果我们尿在瓶子里
but Raj figured out that if you pee in a bottle
然后放进睡袋中
and put it in your sleeping bag,
能有类似热水袋的作用
it helps keep you warm.
这是我们一起住的酒店房间
Here's the hotel room we all share.
到时候我们会单独订一房间的吧
Well, you and I would get our own room, right?
所有酒店都订满了
Every hotel is booked.
不过你看这一块
But, yeah, see this space here
就是我脑袋跟谢尔顿脚底之间的空间
between Sheldon's feet and my head?
到时候你就睡这
That's where you go.
这跟以前打雷的时候谢尔顿
Well, it's no different than when Sheldon
爬上我们床来跟我们挤没什么两样
used to climb in bed with us during a thunderstorm.
不用担心  反正到时候也不太会睡觉
Don't worry, we won't be doing much sleeping anyway.
那里就像个彻夜狂欢派对
It's like an all-night party.
有冷知识竞赛与《龙与地下城》桌游
There's trivia contests and Dungeons & Dragons.
按我们的话说  就是"乐子[锁子甲]超多"
As we like to say, it's "Off the chain mail."
我甚至说了"乐子[锁子甲]超多"
I even said "Off the chain mail,"
她还是没打退堂鼓
and she still wants to go.
或许这事赖我
That's probably my fault.
可能她耳闻了我的超屌邓布利多变装
She may have heard about my cool Dumbledore costume.
行吧  整盒算你20块
Okay, I can give you 20 bucks for the whole box.
这些东西你以前要我几百块呢
But you charged me hundreds for this stuff.
对啊  而且我都不带眨眼的
I know. And I did it with a straight face.
但我需要挣够足够的钱
But I need to earn enough money
我才能去漫展
so I can go to Comic-Con.
好吧
Well... all right.
我给你25块
I'll give you 25 bucks.
我最高就出这么多
That's my best offer.
我也别无选择了
I have no choice.
如果你想挣外快
You know, if you want to make extra money,
我可以给你点活儿啊
I-I could throw some work your way.
真的吗  我什么活儿都愿意做
Really? I'll do anything.
很好  你被录用了
Great, you're hired.
先从把这些东西贴上价钱开始
First thing you can do is put price tags on these.
小的那些先贴50块
Start the little ones at $50.
也没什么
You know, it's no big deal.
反正三天而已  我什么都能忍得住
I can put up with anything for three days.
漫展是五天
Comic-Con's five days.
你耍我吧
Are you kidding me?
你为什么不告诉他你不想去
Why don't you just tell him you don't want to go?
不行  我不想伤他的心
I can't, it'll break his heart.
他总是很努力尝试做那些
You know, he's always making an effort
他不喜欢的事来陪我
to do things with me he doesn't enjoy,
比如出门
like going outside.
他的确是室内猫类型
He is an indoor cat.
或许没想象中那么糟啊
You know, maybe it won't be that bad.
莱纳德说现在宅文化已经是主流文化
Leonard says it's really mainstream now.
漫画不只是给可悲的阿宅看的了
Comic books aren't just for sad nerds anymore.
显然可悲的阿宅在他们族群仍占多数
I mean, it is still a key part of their demographic.
华仔  你能开下门吗
Howie, can you get that?
我在忙
Kind of busy.
有你去圣地亚哥玩耍
Busy like I'll be with the baby
而我在家苦逼带孩子时那么忙吗
if you go to San Diego?
这手套是怎么回事
What's with the gloves?
跟我这身衣服配套的  有何贵干
They complete my ensemble. What do you want?
我想挣点外快
I'm looking to make extra money
来看看你有没有什么杂活给我干
and was wondering if you had any chores I could do.
稍等
Hang on.
妮妮  我可以把我的家务活外包给一个印度人吗
Bernie, can I outsource my chores to an Indian guy?
不行
No.
我尽力了
I tried.
我在考虑
Hey, I was thinking,
如果你想穿情侣装
if you want to do a couples costume,
我们可以把自己刷成绿色  扮成绿巨人和女绿巨人
we could paint ourselves green and be Hulk and She-Hulk.
又或者我们可以把自己刷成蓝色
Or we could paint ourselves blue
扮成夜行者和变形女
and go as Nightcrawler and Mystique.
有没有不用全身刷漆的方案
Is there any scenario where we're not in full body paint?
有啊  如果你想我们看起来逊爆了的话
Yeah, if you want us to look like losers.
你确定其他三人不介意我也一起去吗
Hey, um, are you sure the guys are okay with me coming?
当然啦  为什么这么问
Yeah, of course, why?
就是通常都是你们四个一起去
This is just something you usually do together,
如果我去会破坏气氛  我也不是非得去
and if I'm screwing it up, I don't have to go.
怎么了  你不想去吗
Oh, why? Do you not want to go?
怎么了  你不想我去吗
Why? Do you not want me to go?
不  我当然想你去
No, I want you to go.
那就好  因为我也想去
Okay, good, 'cause that's what I want, too.
现在我们得以绿巨人和女绿巨人的装扮出现
Now we're going as Hulk and She-Hulk.
我不想在漫展上脱掉上衣啊
I don't want to take my shirt off at Comic-Con.
如果我能代漫展发言  我会说我们也不希望这事发生
If I may speak for Comic-Con, we don't want that either.
需要这么毒吗
Is that nice?
不用  但至少诚实啊  而且感觉起来
No, but it's honest, and it sounds like you could use
你们的感情也需要多一点真诚
a little more honesty in your relationship.
实际情况远比嘴上说来得复杂
Uh, I-it's more complicated than that.
我一直诚实对待艾米
I'm always honest with Amy.
有一天她说觉得难为情
The other day she said she was self-conscious
因为肩膀上有颗美人印
about the beauty mark on her shoulder,
而我说  "随你美化你那个美人印
and I said, "You know, you can call that a beauty mark all you want.
但当它上面长了根毛  那它就是个痣"
When there's hair growing out of it, that's a mole."
你觉得她也对你如此诚实吗
Do you think she's as honest with you?
我希望是如此
I should hope so.
当她称我为没心没肺的混蛋时
When she called me an insensitive jerk,
我会希望她是真心的
I'd like to think she meant it.
肯定有其他让你挣外快的法子
There's got to be other ways you can make a quick buck.
哪这么容易找
Yeah, you'd think.
或许我可以去卖血卖精子
Ooh, maybe I could sell my blood and sperm.
我真应该在脖子上系个铃铛
I really should wear a bell around my neck
这样我一来  你们就能听见
so you guys can hear me coming.
来  我帮你吧
Here, let me help you.
谢谢
Thank you.
双层夹心奥利奥
Oh, Double Stuf Oreos,
我还记得当初我吃得起的日子
I remember when I could afford you.
哈雷又哭了
There she goes.
你待着  我去吧
Stay, I'll get her.
-非常感谢  -不客气
- Appreciate it. - That's fine.
我可以和她一起抱头痛哭
She and I can cry together.
他真是个好人
He's such a sweetie.
我知道  真希望我们能有办法帮他
I know, I wish there was some way we could help him.
如果他可以找到一个薪水高的女朋友
If he could find a girl with a good job,
那他所有的问题将迎刃而解
all his problems would be over.
是啊  看我现在过得多"好"
Yeah, that's working out great for me.
佩妮说他们准备好出发了
Penny says they're ready to go.
很好
Very well.
准备迎接漫长的欺骗夜吧
Prepare for a long night of deceit.
谢尔顿  女人可以化妆  那不叫欺骗
Sheldon, women can wear makeup, it's not lying.
我刚说的是莱纳德
I was talking about Leonard.
而且如果化妆品这么诚我不欺
And if makeup is so truthful,
那为什么有化妆品叫"遮瑕膏"[隐瞒者]
why is it called "Concealer"?
等等  莱纳德欺骗什么了
Wait, wait, wait, what's Leonard lying about?
他其实不想佩妮去漫展
He doesn't really want Penny to go to Comic-Con.
他是为了让她开心才带她去
He's just doing it to make her happy.
真的吗
Really?
因为佩妮其实并不想去漫展
Because she doesn't actually want to go.
她是为了让他开心才跟他去
She's just doing it to make him happy.
所以他们俩的本意是想让对方开心
So they're both trying to make each other happy,
而结果却是让彼此恶心吗
and the end result is they make each other sad?
真是太可笑了
That's hilarious.
我等不及要告诉他们了
I can't wait to tell them.
不  你不能拆穿他们
No, you're not gonna tell them anything.
你不许插手这件事
You're gonna stay out of it.
为什么
Why?
因为这是他们之间的事
Because it's between them.
你难道没注意到吗
Well, if you haven't noticed,
过去十年里我一直生活在他们之间
I've been between them for the last ten years.
宝贝  你想开车吗
Hey, babe, you want to drive?
当然  不过你开也行
Sure, or you can.
没关系  我知道你不喜欢我开车的方式
No, it's fine, I know you don't like the way I drive.
我对你开车技术没有意见啊
I don't have a problem with your driving.
你听见他们的鬼话了吗
Are you listening to this?
他们在所有事情上都欺骗对方
They deceive each other about everything.
我告诉你  是停车场那家伙撞我
Just so you know, that guy in the parking lot hit me.
他当时都不在车上好吗  不过行吧
He wasn't in a car, but okay.
你直说你想开不得了
Just say you want to drive.
我真的不想开
I honestly don't.
艾米  帮个忙  你开车吧
Amy, do us a favor, please drive.
好  乐意效劳
Sure, happy to.
如果你想开车  那就开啊
If you want to drive, just drive.
我不懂为什么要搞得这么复杂
I don't see why this has to be so complicated.
一点都不复杂  艾米开车  就这样
It's not complicated. Amy's driving, that's it!
才不是  谁都看得出你不高兴
That's not it because you're clearly upset.
你才是看上去不高兴的那个
You're the one who seems upset.
我为什么要不高兴
Why would I be upset?
因为你不想她去参加漫展
Because you don't want her to go to Comic-Con!
这种"不插手"的方式真是相当有意思啊
This is an interesting way to stay out of it.
慢着  你不想我去吗
Wait, you don't want me to go?
我只是觉得你不会觉得好玩
Well, I just don't think you're gonna have a good time.
是啊  听好了
Yeah, well, get this:
佩妮也是这么想的
neither does Penny,
所以她并不想去
that's why she doesn't want to go.
你下套  我下刀  合作无间
You set 'em up, I knock 'em down, good job.
如果你不想去  为什么你不直说
Why would you say you wanted to go if you didn't?
我本以为跟着去会让你开心
I just thought it would make you happy.
好吧  等等  如果你不想跟去
O-O-O-Okay, hold on, so if you don't want to go
而我也不必带你去
and I don't need to bring you,
我们还是恩爱好夫妻吧
is everything good?
等等  我先决定我是不是在生你气
Hold on, I'm trying to decide if I'm mad at you.
不会  不用去我很开心
No, I'm happy I don't have to go.
好啦  问题解决
All right, problem solved.
-没错  -对
- Okay. - Yeah.
还没完呢  刚才不是还在吵谁开车吗
Not entirely, the fight over who's going to drive is still...
天啊  快把嘴闭上
Oh, my God, stop talking!
家里看着好干净啊
The place looks great.
你们请佣人了吗
Did you guys get a maid?
算是吧
Kind of.
晚餐快好了
Dinner's almost ready.
如果你们喜欢烘肉卷  那肯定会喜欢它的表亲
If you like meatloaf, I'm sure you'll like its cousin,
大碗肉
bowl of meat.
如果你还想着挣外快
Hey, if you're still looking to make money,
我愿意付钱让你把外套烧了
I will pay you to burn that jacket.
谢谢  但看来今年
Thank you, but it doesn't look like
我是无缘漫展了
I'm going to Comic-Con this year.
你有这么多债务在身
Well, with as much debt as you have,
明年应该也不能去
probably not next year either.
-华仔  -好的
- Howie? - Sure.
这是给你的
This is for you.
这是什么
What's this?
补发工资  之前你给我们当保姆
It's back pay for all the babysitting
还有照顾哈雷的酬劳
and taking care of Halley you've done.
里面的钱就算你去参加漫展还绰绰有余
There's more than enough in there to cover Comic-Con.
我也帮忙照顾哈雷了啊
Um, I also take care of Halley.
你也在这里白住了啊
And you live here for free.
的确如此  夫人  多谢收留  夫人
I do, ma'am, thank you, ma'am.
你们真是太慷慨了
This is so generous of you,
我...我都不知道该说什么了
I-I, um, I don't know what to say.
现在你可以跟我们一起去了
Now you can come with us.
对啊  谢尔顿脚边还有地方睡哦
Yeah, there's room in the bed by Sheldon's feet.
尽管我很感激你们给我这笔钱
As much as I appreciate this,
可我不能收
I can't accept it.
好吗
Okay?
哈雷是我的教女
Halley's my goddaughter,
我照顾她是应该的  不是为了钱
I don't take care of her for money.
我是
I would.
留着吧  就当是我们送你的礼物
Keep it. Consider it a gift.
等等  这到底是补发工资还是礼物
Hold on. Is it back pay or is it a gift?
有什么区别吗
What's the difference?
当我们被关在不同房间被国税局审问时
When the IRS questions us in separate rooms,
我们的答案必须一致啊
we need to have our stories straight.
无所谓啦  反正我不会收下
It doesn't matter. I'm not keeping this.
我正努力自食其力  做一个有担当的人
I'm trying to pay my own way and be responsible.
拿别人给的钱可不行
Taking handouts won't help that.
所以你不去参加漫展了吗
So you're not going to Comic-Con?
反正我去过很多次了
I've been plenty of times.
少去一次也没关系  我是个成年人了
If I miss one, it's fine. I'm a big boy.
我也是成年人  但如果我少去了一次
I'm a big boy, and if I missed one,
我就会发成年人的脾气
I'd throw a big-boy tantrum.
其实我都去了12次了
You know what? I've gone 12 times.
要不今年我也不参加了吧
Maybe I'll sit out this year, too.
-真的吗  -真的
- Really? - Yeah.
或许我们那周末可以找点好玩的事情干
Maybe you and I can do something fun that weekend.
一起去漂流怎么样
Ooh, how about white-water rafting?
不如我们折中一下
Oh... how about we compromise
去迪士尼玩小小世界之旅
and go on the Small World ride at Disneyland?
乘坐小船游览由身穿各地民族服饰的木偶
和活动布景组成的全球七大洲
要不我也不去了
You know what, I'm not gonna go either.
我现在身为人父
I'm a father now.
我更愿意跟家人待在一起
I'd rather spend time with my family.
你只是不想跟谢尔顿两人一起去
You just don't want to go alone with Sheldon.
我去看看晚餐好了没
I'm gonna go check on dinner.
听起来大家都不去了
Sounds like everyone's staying home.
那你怎么说
What do you say?
谁不去谁傻逼  反正我是要去
Nuts to that, I'm going to Comic-Con!
就你自己去吗
By yourself?
不一定啊
Not necessarily.
我还有四个月的时间找新朋友陪我去
I have four months to find some new friends.
我陪你去
I'll go with you.
你人真好  斯图尔特
That's very kind of you, Stuart.
等七月的时候你再问我一次
Check back in with me in July.
瞧瞧我的漂亮女友
There's my pretty girlfriend.
我是不会跟你去漫展的
I'm not going with you to Comic-Con.
干嘛  难道就不能因为见到自己女人很开心
What? Can't a man just be happy to see his woman
然后就拍拍她第二性感的部位
and pat her on her second most erogenous
球窝关节吗
ball-and-socket joint?
能啊  但我还是不会改变主意
He can, but it's still not changing my mind.
或许我裤裆里的东西能让你改变主意
Well, maybe what's in my pants will change your mind.
这是今年明星座谈会的嘉宾名单
It's a list of this year's panelists.
很长  对不对
It's long, isn't it?